Citizens Environmental Coalition; Records apap197
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Activities, 1973-2005; 1; 22.35 cubic ft.
  - Hazardous Waste Sites, 1980-2005; 1.2; 4.5 cubic ft.
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 5, 1992; 2002 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 5, Sherman / Lazerne, 1997 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 5, Ticonderoga Transfer Station, Ticonderoga, 1987; 2001-2005 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, 1990-1999 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Anitec Image Corporation, Binghamton, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Armstrong Cork Landfills, Volney, 1995 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Cayuga County Groundwater Contamination, Aurelius, Fleming & Springport, 2002 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Carosel Center Mall, Pyramid Companies, Oil City, 1990 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 8)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Fulton Safe Drinking Water Action Committee for Environmental Concerns (FSDWAC) / Central New York Toxics Association (CNYTA), Fulton, 1987-1993 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Clothier Drum Proposal Site, 1983-1987 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Colonial Cleaners, Lansing, 1991-1997 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Ithaca Area, 1984-1992 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 12)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Jacksonville Gasoline Spill, Mobil Oil Corporation, Jacksonville / Ulysses, 1984-1988 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Landstrom Landfill, Tioga & Tompkins Counties, 1985-1989 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Novak Farm, McDonough, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 15)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Onondaga Lake, 1995-1997 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 16)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Oswego Area, 1983-1987 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 17)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Pollution Abatement Services (PAS), 1987-1995 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Rosen Brothers / Scrap King, Cortland, 1996-1998 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Solvent Savers, Linklaen, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Syracuse Area, 1983-1991 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Whitehall Landfill, Whitestown, 1996-1999 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, 1989-2003 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, Akzo Nobel Salt, Retsof, 1987-1999; 4 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 24-27)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, Guardian Glass / Guardian Industries Corp., Geneva, 1992; 1994-1999; 2 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 28-29)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, Linden Tech Industrial Park, Brighton, Penfield, 1991-1996 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 30)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 9, 102nd Street Landfill, Niagara Falls, 2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 31)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 9, Hickory Woods Subdivision, Buffalo, 1999-2001; 4 folders (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 1-4)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 1, NTU Circuits, Bayshore, 1991-1996 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 1, Port Washington Landfill, North Hempstead, 1982-1995 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 1, Syosset Landfill, 1983-1986 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 3, 1985-2005 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 3, Bernal Well, Germantown, 1982-1986 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 3, Marathon Battery Company, Cold Spring, 1985-1991 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 3, Old Nyack / Dexter Landfill / Pyramid Mall Project, West Nyack, 1974-1995 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 3, Rotron-Woodstock, Woodstock, 1995-2002 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 8)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 4, Schenectady Chemicals / Schenectady International, Rotterdam Junction / Schenectady, 1989-2004 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Clay Landfill PCBs, Clay, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Fulton Terminals, Fulton, 1986-1989 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 7, Volney Landfill, Volney, 1980-1989 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 12)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, Akzo Nobel Salt, Retsof, 1987-1999 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 8, Brockport (3 sites), 2000-2001 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 9, Hickory Woods Subdivision, Buffalo, 1999-2001 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 15)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, DEC Region 4, Dewey Loeffel Landfill, Nassau, 1997-2005 (Flat-file 1)
  - Health Care Without Harm, 1994-2002; 1.3; 4.1 cubic ft. and 2 videotapes
    The records in the subseries Health Care Without Harm (HCWH) consist of contact information, correspondence, surveys, brochures, meeting minutes, planning documents, research material, conference records, fact sheets, and publications (draft and final). Additional material such as slides, videotapes, and HCWH pins are present as well. In New York State, Health Care Without Harm focused on environmental concerns in health care, particularly in hospitals. CEC collected research material about environmental issues in health care dating back to 1994, two years prior to the founding of the national Health Care Without Harm campaign in Bolinas, California. The earliest records documenting CEC activities in the HCWH campaign were those related to dioxin and incineration activities. As its activity level increased, CEC became involved in efforts to stimulate environmentally friendly purchasing policies and improve waste management in hospitals, which led to publications such as Environmentally Preferable Purchasing and "Greening" Hospitals, as well as a conference called "Cutting Costs, Reducing Waste, and Buying Smart". Outreach records discuss mercury reduction, waste management efforts, worker safety, and patient safety issues. A significant amount of the records document activity in New York City, particularly after a grant-funded coordinator was hired to focus on advocacy in this part of the state. CEC's records include an Environmental Curriculum for Healthcare Administrators completed in 2002.
    - Contacts, 1994-2001 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Contacts and Outreach, 1996-2000; 6 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 2-7)
    - Cutting Costs, Reducing Waste, and Buying Smart, 1998 October 29; 3 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 8-10)
    - Cutting Costs, Reducing Waste, and Buying Smart, Follow Up, 1998 October 29 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Environmentally Preferable Purchasing, 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 12-13)
    - "Greening" Hospitals, 1998; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 14-15)
    - HCWH NYC, 1999-2002; 6 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 16-21)
    - National Campaign, 1998-2001 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - Pins, Undated (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - Planning, 1999-2001 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 24)
    - Resources, Other States, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 25)
    - Slides, Undated (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 26)
    - Waste Management, 1998-2001; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 27-28)
    - Environmental Curriculum, 2002; 7 folders (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 1-7)
    - Pollution Prevention Kit for Nurses (part of Waste Management), Undated (Box 3 (1-Activities), Item 1)
    - Environmentally Safe Hospitals, Resources, 1998 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Environmentally Safe Hospitals, Comments, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Environmentally Safe Hospitals, Original, 2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Environmentally Safe Hospitals, Conference, 2000 October 12 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Environmentally Safe Hospitals, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - Healthcare and Dioxin, 1996-2000; 4 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 6-9)
    - Incineration, 1997-1999; 3 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 10-12)
    - Latex, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - Mercury, 1998-2000; 2 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 14-15)
    - Mercury, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 16)
    - Mercury, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 17-18)
    - Needlesticks, 1998-2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - Pesticides, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - PVC, 1998-2000 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - Resources, 1995-2001; 6 folders (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 22-27)
    - Resources Guide, Research, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 28)
    - Waste Management, 1998-2001 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 29)
    - Waste Reduction Manual for Hospitals and Health Care Facilities, 1999 (Box 4 (1-Activities), Folder 30)
    - Resources, 1996-2000; 8 folders (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 1-8)
    - Resources, 1997 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - Resources, 1999 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - Resources, 2000 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Resources, 2000-2002; 4 folders (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 12-15)
    - Resources, 2001 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 16)
    - Resources, Healing the Harm, 1996-2000 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 17)
    - Resources, Setting Healthcare's Environmental Agenda, 2000 October 16 (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - Resources, Wisconsin Mercury Source Book, 1997; 3 folders (Box 5 (1-Activities), Folder 19-21)
    - Blue Vinyl: A Toxic Comedy for the Whole Family, Documentary, Flyer, 2002 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - First Do No Harm: Polyvinyl Chloride and Medicine's Responsibility, Videotape, Promotional Letter, 2000 (Box 6 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Contacts and Outreach, 1996-2000 (Box 7 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Cutting Costs, Reducing Waste, and Buying Smart, 1998 October 29 (Box 7 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Mercury, 2001 (Box 7 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Blue Vinyl: A Toxic Comedy for the Whole Family, Documentary, VHS Videotape, 2002; VHS videotape (Video-tape 1)
    - First Do No Harm: Polyvinyl Chloride and Medicine's Responsibility, 2000; VHS videotape (Video-tape 2)
  - Healthy Schools, Youth, and the Environment, 1991-1996; 1.4; 0.17 cubic ft.
    The materials in this subseries are concerned with environmental issues in schools and playgrounds and contain educational materials for and pro-environment actions by youth. The records include reports, articles, guides, and brochures.
    - Healthy Schools Network, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Rochester's Perilous Playgrounds, 1993 September (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Youth and the Environment, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
  - Hudson River PCBs, 1986-2002; 1.5; 0.17 cubic ft.
    This series contains articles, petitions, news releases, correspondence, and an action plan, concerned with PCBs in the Hudson River. General Electric (GE) plays an important role, being the main source of this pollution.
    - Hudson River PCBs, 1986-2002; 3 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 1-3)
  - Kodak, 1989-2004; 1.6; 2.20 cubic ft.
    The records in this subseries include correspondence, research material, press releases, and brochures related to Eastman Kodak. The records document efforts to reduce toxic emissions and promote a safer environment in communities near Eastman Kodak locations in Rochester, NY. CEC became formally involved with Kodak environmental issues when the former joined the Kandid Coalition in 1997. With thirteen other organizations, CEC advocated for improved environmental management and first class labor relations. This subseries includes outreach material and extensive research records for Kodak's Toxic Colors and A Tarnished Image: The Eastman Kodak Performance Scorecard. The earliest dated material is background information on Kodak's company policies and practices from 1989. Much of the information in A Tarnished Image was collected from systematic Freedom of Information Law requests. The research material includes information from: the Department of Labor (DOL), Occupational Safety and Health Association (OSHA), Workfare programs, Kodak Annual Reports, Kodak Environmental Report, New York State Department of Tax and Finance, and the Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry (ATSDR). A Tarnished Image was a joint publication of CEC and the New York State Labor and the Environment Network. Notes and drafts for the Kodak Corporate Accountability Campaign and Kodak shareholders' environmental resolution are present as well.
    - Agency Letters, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - Agency for Toxic Substance and Disease Registry, Cancer Studies, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - CEO Compensation, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Corporate Articles, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Datacenter Research, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1992-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Undated (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
    - Directory of Shareholder Affiliations, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 8)
    - Economic Development, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - Empire State Development Corporation, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - Employer Stats, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Facilities Corporation, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Violations, 1991-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - ESDC/DED, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - ESDC/DED, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 15)
    - Executive Excess '98, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 16)
    - Guide to a Fair Economic Policy for New York State, 1998 March (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 17)
    - Guide to Federal Welfare Reform, Volume II, 1997 February (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - IDAs, 1992-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - Job Training Programs, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - Job Training Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - Kodak, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - Kodak Articles, 1990-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - Kodak Articles, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 24)
    - Kodak Antiunion Activities, 1989-1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 25)
    - Kodak Finances, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 26)
    - Kodak and New York State Tax and Finance, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 27)
    - KPW Site, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 28)
    - Lawsuits, 1990-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 29)
    - Lawsuits, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 30)
    - Layoffs, 1994-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 31)
    - Legislature, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Anti-Environment Affiliations, 1993-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 33)
    - NAFTA, 1991; 1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 34)
    - New York Power Authority, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 35)
    - NLRB, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 36)
    - New York State Department of Labor, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 37)
    - New York State Department of Labor, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 38)
    - NYSERDA, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 39)
    - Original Draft Scorecard, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 40)
    - OSHA, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 41)
    - Press Release Advisories, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 42)
    - Recommendations, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 43)
    - Shareholder Resolution Information, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 44)
    - Stockholders, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 45)
    - A Tarnished Image: The Eastman Kodak Performance Scorecard, 1998 April 30 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 46)
    - Workface New York State, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 47)
    - Background Information, 1990-1997 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - CEC and Kodak, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - CEC Letters and Leaflets, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Contributions to Monroe County State Senators and Other Legislators, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Contributions to Monroe County State Senators and Other Legislators, 1994-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - FEC Data Federal NY Campaigns, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - FEC Data Federal NY Campaigns, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
    - FEC Data Federal NY Campaigns, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 8)
    - FEC Data Federal NY Campaigns, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - Karl Breyman FOIL Requests, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - Kodak Activities, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - Kodak Activities, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 12-13)
    - Kodak Activities, 2000-2004 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - Kodak Activities, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 15-16)
    - Kodak Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 17)
    - Kodak Flyers, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - Kodak PAC Contributions and Members, 1993-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - Kodak Summary, 2002 August (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - Kodak Website, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - Monroe County Guide to Elected Officials, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - PAC Contributions, 1995-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - Soft Money Contributions and Individual Employees, 1993-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 24)
    - CEC and Kodak, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - CEC Letters and Leaflets, 1996-1998 (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - IDAs, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Kodak News Clippings, Undated; 2 folders (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 4-5)
    - Kodak Flyers, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - Shareholder Resolution Information, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
  - Labor and the Environment Network, 1989-2001; 1.7; 2.37 cubic ft. and 1 videotape
    The records in the Labor and the Environment (LEN) subseries include conference files, reports, correspondence, outreach documents, safety manuals, photographs, research material, and news clippings. These records relate to the common concerns shared by labor activists and environmentalists in New York State. The records reflect activities to inform and strengthen the partnership between laborers and environmental advocates. Many records pertain to the LEN conferences organized by CEC, beginning with the first conference in 1989. Records related to the drafting and March 1998 publication of Keeping Score: A New York Guide to Researching Industry Performance on the Environment, Labor, and Government Subsidies are found in this subseries as well.
    - Corporate Welfare Accountability Report, 1995; 3 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 1-3)
    - Corporate Welfare and LEN, 1995; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 4-5)
    - Frank Johnson, LEN Speaker, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 6)
    - Keeping Score, Comments, 1997 Fall (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 7)
    - Keeping Score, Final with Addendums, 1998 March (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 8)
    - Labor and Environment Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - LEN Conference, Attendees and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - LEN Conference, Thank You Notes and Contact Information, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - LEN Conference Budgets, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 12)
    - LEN Conference, Environmental News and Registration Form, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - LEN Conference, Thank You Notes, Evaluation and Summary Forms, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - LEN Conference, Sign up Sheets and Housing List, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 15)
    - LEN Conference, "Building a Movement" Information, 1991; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 16-17)
    - LEN Conference, Workshop Needs and Summaries, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - LEN Conference, Assortment of Information, includes Evaluation Forms and Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - LEN Conference, Participation Lists and News Releases, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - LEN Conference, Programs, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - LEN Conference, News Packet and Guide, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - LEN Conference, Newsletters and Publications, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - LEN Conference, Newsletters and Reports, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 24)
    - LEN Conference, Brochures, 1994; 1995; 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 25)
    - LEN Conference, Evaluations, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 26)
    - LEN Conference, Resource List, Guides, and Evaluation Forms, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 27)
    - LEN Conference, Evaluations, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 28)
    - Sample Post Conference Handout, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Activities), Folder 29)
    - Corporate Accountability, 2001 October 04 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 1)
    - The Great Louisiana Tax Giveaway, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 2)
    - Jobs and the Environment, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 3)
    - Jobs and Environmental Training, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 4)
    - Labor and the Environment Outreach, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 5)
    - Labor and the Environment Retreat, 1992-1993; 3 folders (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 6-8)
    - LEN, Environment Information, including the US-Mexican Free Trade Agreement, 1989-1993 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 9)
    - LEN, Agendas, 1992-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 10)
    - LEN, "Building a Movement" Information, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 11)
    - LEN, Thank You Notes and Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 12)
    - LEN, Chemical Agriculture, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 13)
    - LEN, Corporate Pollution, 1994-1997 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 14)
    - LEN, "Jobs and the Environment", 1994-1997 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 15)
    - LEN, Accountability Report and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 16)
    - LEN, Budget, Program, and Participation List, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 17)
    - LEN, Correspondence with other Organizations, 1999 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 18)
    - LEN, Minutes and Meeting Plans, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 19)
    - LEN Resources, 1990-1995 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 20)
    - LEN Resources, 1990-1998 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 21)
    - LEN Resources, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 22)
    - LEN Resources, 1994; 1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 23)
    - LEN Resources, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (1-Activities), Folder 24)